<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Allen T. Capdeboscq, Jr.]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[allen-t-capdeboscq-jr]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea93f73e09de3]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:52:18 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Mon Nov 07 2022 18:13:57 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/626d8226d543d733c59086db_61e02eb1968ff93a90a7543e_Allen%20T%20Capdeboscq_.jpeg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Allen T. Capdeboscq, Jr., Chief Financial Officer]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Financial Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Chief Financial Officer of EmpowerMe Wellness, Allen Capdeboscq has primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all the finance activities of the company, including strategic planning and budgeting, cash flow management, and capital structure/financing activities. As a seasoned finance professional, Capdeboscq brings over 20 years of experience in corporate financial planning, mergers and acquisitions, commercial development, and investment banking. Allen has a passion for value creation, continuous improvement, and getting behind the numbers.
Allen joins EmpowerMe after a 15-year career with Peabody Energy Corporation. Throughout his 15-year career at Peabody, he served in roles of increasing responsibility including Vice President – Global Corporate Development, Vice President – Capital and Financial Planning, Senior Vice President – Commercial and Marketing Support, and Senior Vice President – Global Corporate Development and Special Projects. Prior to Peabody, Allen was an investment banker with A.G. Edwards for four years serving middle-market energy clients with capital raising and financial advisory assignments.
Allen received his Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering with honors from Louisiana State University and his Master of Business Administration from the Kellogg School of Management at Northwestern University in Evanston, IL. Allen and his beautiful wife, Jody, reside in St. Louis with their three children and three Labrador retrievers.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Chief Financial Officer of EmpowerMe Wellness, Allen Capdeboscq has primary responsibility for the planning, implementation...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[5]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Amanda Kern]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[amanda-kern]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea94acae0a106]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Aug 30 2022 18:09:50 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:40:18 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4aed1ef596000b6350755_Kern_Amanda.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Amanda Kern]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[therapy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Amanda is a Speech Language Pathologist with 10 years of experience working with geriatrics in Skilled Nursing, Assisted Living, and Memory Care settings as a Treating Clinician, Lead Therapist, and Agency Administrator. She obtained her master’s degree in Speech Language Pathology from Southern Illinois University Edwardsville. Amanda is an active member of ASHA. She is VitalStim and MDTP certified. As the Area Rehab Director, Amanda is able to provide development and oversight of area-wide patient care and operational support to rehab teams, implement clinical programs, and optimize patient’s success. Amanda lives in Waterloo, IL with her husband and three sons. Amanda loves spending time with her family and making memories that will be cherished for a lifetime.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Amanda is a Speech Language Pathologist with 10 years of experience working with geriatrics in Skilled Nursing, Assisted Living, and Memory Care settings as a Treating Clinician, Lead Therapist, and Agency Administrator.]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[33]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Brad Andrews]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[brad-andrews]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9d010e0a0f7]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Fri Jun 17 2022 17:35:38 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:34:20 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ad69a61c7ba816659376_Andrews_Brad.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Senior Vice President, Product Implementations]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Senior Vice President, Product Implementations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Brad brings over 14 years of experience to senior care. His career has allowed him to problem-solve barriers and provide top-tier and unparalleled care to seniors both today and into the future. He enjoys assessing situations, problem-solving, and developing strategies. Brad graduated from University at Buffalo’s School of Health and Health Professions in 2008 with a Doctor of Physical Therapy. After graduation, he worked as a Physical Therapist until 2013, when he became the Co-CEO of startup Salus Physical Therapy. In April of 2022, Salus was acquired by EmpowerMe wellness and Brad became the SVP of Product Implementations. In addition to his passion for helping seniors live happy and healthier lives, he likes challenges that involve long durations of concentration - whether it be an analysis or an endurance sporting event. Brad currently resides in the Tampa Bay area with his wife Alex and their two German Shepherds. A Buffalonian at heart, Brad devotes his Sundays to the Buffalo Bills for a good portion of the year and considers himself lucky to be a Floridian for 15 years. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Brad brings over 14 years of experience to senior care. His career has allowed him to problem solve barriers and provide top-tier and unparalleled care to seniors both today and into the future. He enjoys assessing situations, problem-solving, and developing strategies...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[15]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Carrie Ward, SPHR]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[carrie-ward-sphr]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9165be0a119]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:34:47 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:56:15 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63bf1d3ac8cd2d585429120f_Carrie%20Ward-web.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Carrie Ward, SPHR,Chief People Officer]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief People Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As Chief People Officer, Carrie leads EmpowerMe’s Human Resources and Recruitment efforts, working to provide our team members with the best possible employee experience. Carrie has an extensive history of leading companies through periods of rapid expansion. Formerly Chief Human Resources Officer for GardaWorld and Chief Operating Officer for Major Brands, Inc., Ward’s expertise spans multiple disciplines and has created substantial value for the companies she has served.
A magna cum laude graduate of St. Louis University’s John Cook School of Business, Carrie has earned black belt Six Sigma certification. She is active with a number of civic service organizations, serving on the boards for the United Way of Greater St. Louis, Banded Brigade Outdoors, and the Veteran’s Business Resource Center. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As Chief People Officer, Carrie leads EmpowerMe’s Human Resources and Recruitment efforts, working to provide our team members with the best possible employee experience. ]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[5]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Casey Griebel, MSN, FNP-C]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[casey-griebel-msn-fnp-c]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea91676e09ec3]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 16:01:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:40:52 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/630fbf3a2c7716b267022a4f_Griebel_C-min%20(1).jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Casey Griebel, MSN, APRN, FNP-C ]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Casey Griebel has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care. Casey brings over 10 years of nursing experience, with nearly two years as a Nurse Practitioner. She has in-depth focus and collaboration skills, with experience in acute care, oncology, home health, outpatient, and hospice. Casey has completed numerous Nurse Practitioner clinical rotations at some of the top hospital systems in the St. Louis area, including Barnes Jewish Hospital West, SSM-St. Mary’s, and Compass Health. She most recently worked as a Nurse Practitioner at MinuteClinic in St. Louis, MO. Casey received her Bachelor of Science in Nursing with honors from Saint Louis University and her Master of Science in Nursing from Saint Louis University, Trudy Busch Valentine School of Nursing. She has numerous licensures and certifications, including American Academy of Nurse Practitioners Certification Board (NP-C), American Nurses Credentialing Center (RN), and AHA Basic Life Support for the Healthcare Professional (BLS). She is licensed as a Registered Nurse in the states of Missouri and Illinois and is additionally licensed as a Nurse Practitioner in the State of Missouri.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Casey Griebel has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[6]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Cathy Coleman, ANP]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[cathy-coleman-anp]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea98cf6e09fc7]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 15:54:57 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:42:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/62a0c6406ea6e7bd05c35950_Coleman_C-min.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Cathy ColeMan, ANP]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Cathy Coleman has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care. As a seasoned nurse practitioner, Cathy brings over 30 years of experience in nursing and 11 years as a Nurse Practitioner. Her breadth of expertise includes general medicine, emergency medicine, primary care, long-term
care, hospice care, palliative care, nursing education- Adjunct Professor, and quality
improvement/staff development. Cathy joins EmpowerMe with an extensive portfolio, working for the top hospital systems in the St. Louis metro area, including Barnes Jewish Hospital and Christian Hospital Northeast. She most recently spent the past 5 years at SSM-St. Luke’s Hospital as a Nurse Practitioner. Cathy received her Bachelor of Science in Nursing from Webster University and her Master of Science in Nursing from Goldfarb School of Nursing at Barnes-Jewish College. She holds certifications for Thanatology and Healthcare Ethics and has advanced certification as a Hospice and Palliative Care Nurse. She is currently licensed as a Registered Nurse and Nurse Practitioner in the state of Missouri.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Cathy Coleman has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[29]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Chastity Warrington]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[chastity-warrington]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea9d570e09136]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:26:39 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 04 2023 14:38:04 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Chastity Warrington, Regional Vice President, Diagnostic Sales]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Diagnostics]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President, Diagnostic Sales]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Chastity is the Regional Vice President - Diagnostic Sales at EmpowerMe Wellness. She has spent her 20+ years in healthcare overseeing sales, operations, and client satisfaction for health systems, laboratories, post-acute networks, and consulting services. In her role with EmpowerMe, she focuses on helping both new and existing clients identify their diagnostic needs. Enabling them to implement on-site diagnostic care, improving the lives of their senior living communities. I love being a part of the much-needed change that we're making in the senior living community, while at the same time ensuring that we're providing the best service from all aspects! Diagnostic services help our client communities and the residents they serve receive care in their home environment. We're able to aid in the monitoring of disease states a resident may be experiencing as well as keep those that are healthy on the right track. We have a unique opportunity to have a big impact on the Senior Living community. I'm so proud to be a part of a company that's forward-thinking and making a change in the industry that's been needed for years. In addition, she oversees the Account Management team focusing on the implementation and continued client satisfaction for diagnostic services. Chastity lives in Perry, MO with her husband and has two adult children.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Chastity is the Regional Vice President - Diagnostic Sales at EmpowerMe Wellness. She has spent her 20+ years in...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Craig M. Sever BS R. Ph.]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[craig-m-sever-bs-r-ph]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea96a97e0a10e]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:36:28 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:43:11 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af7ed3a552dbf8ceac19_Sever_Craig.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Craig M. Sever BS R. Ph., Clinical Coordinator, Pharmacy.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacy]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Clinical Coordinator, Pharmacy]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Craig has been with EverSpring for over five years and is responsible for the management and oversight of the day-to-day clinical operations of pharmacy services in senior living and developmentally delayed communities.
As a 1987 graduate of St. Louis College of Pharmacy, Craig spent 13 years as a clinical pharmacist in a 500-bed, acute-bed hospital specializing in infectious disease, trauma, and intensive care while serving 10+ of those years as an Adjunct Professor for the college. For the past 22 years, he has specialized as a Consultant Pharmacist concentrating on the Developmentally Delayed and Geriatric population. He is also ASCP Disease Trainingship qualified in Osteoporosis and Cardiology.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Craig has been with EverSpring for over five years and is responsible for the management and oversight of the day-to-day clinical operations of pharmacy services in...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[22]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[David Church]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[david-church]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea95bc5e0a0fe]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Mon Jan 17 2022 11:43:24 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:38:18 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae57403895797f6ef7ff_Church_David.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[David Church, Vice President, Clinical Strategy & Innovation]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President, Clinical Strategy & Innovation]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[David joined the EmpowerMe team in 2018 and has led the effort to build robust and scalable financial and reimbursement systems. Prior to joining the team, David spent 15 years as Director of Finance and Operations, reporting to the CEO, for a chain of clinics providing rehab, primary care and pain management services with annual revenue exceeding $20 million. David holds bachelor degrees in both Exercise Physiology and Business Administration from Southern Illinois University and a Master of Business Administration from Webster University. He resides in O’Fallon, Illinois with his wife of ten years and three children. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[David joined the EmpowerMe team in 2018 and has led the effort to build robust and scalable financial and reimbursement systems. Prior to joining the team...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[19]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Diana Daniels, MPT, COMT, MBA ]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[diana-daniels-mpt-comt-mba]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea93605e09fce]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 18:15:14 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 27 2022 18:58:11 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/62a0e2c04c69f1d1ae9e20ae_Daniel_D-min.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Diana Daniels, MPT, COMT, MBA ]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Diana is a Physical Therapist with 19 years of experience. She graduated from Rockhurst University in Kansas City, MO with her BA in Psychology and then her master’s in physical therapy. Diana achieved her orthopedic manual certification from Maitland-Australian Physiotherapy. Additionally, in 2012, Diana obtained her MBA from Lindenwood University in St. Charles, MO with an emphasis on business management. Diana has had a focused career on team-building strategies and servant leadership throughout her years of service in healthcare. You are likely to find Diana involved in watching her girls play volleyball, soccer, and basketball. Diana currently lives in O’Fallon, MO with her husband and 2 daughters.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Diana is a Physical Therapist with 19 years of experience. She graduated from Rockhurst University in Kansas City, MO with her BA in Psychology and then her master’s in physical therapy...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[27]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Emily Stone]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[emily-stone]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea98114e09c6d]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 10:07:19 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 22:10:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/61e00423e0198a44375ee548_Rectangle%2092.png]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Area Rehab Director]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Emily is a physical therapist with over 23 years of experience in outpatient settings and senior living facilities. Emily has a Master’s of Science…]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Emily is a physical therapist with over 23 years of experience in outpatient settings and senior living facilities. Emily has a Master’s of Science…]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[8]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Erik Painter, MHA, COTA/L]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[erik-painter-mha-cota-l]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9fc8ce0a10c]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Sun Jan 16 2022 08:13:43 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:42:25 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af4e463bd5ead6cce6a9_Painter_Eric.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Erik Painter, MHA, COTA/L, Vice President of Strategic Projects]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President of Strategic Projects]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Erik has 22 years of clinical experience as a COTA/L with a Master’s in Health Administration from Webster University. He has held several leadership positions for a large national therapy provider recently directing all regulatory compliance for 40 Rehab Agencies. Erik is currently a Medicare surveyor with AAAASF. He serves on the policy committee with NARA (National Association of Rehab Agencies). He is Accreditation Evaluator of ACOTE (Accreditation Council for Occupational Therapy Education).
Erik lives in Belleville, IL, has been married to Blair for 26 years and has two dogs and a cat. He loves to camp, watch TV, and read.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Erik has 22 years of clinical experience as a COTA/L with a Master’s in Health Administration from Webster University. He has held several leadership positions for a large national therapy provider...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[26]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Hayley Cichacki, PHR, SHRM-CP]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[hayley-cichacki-phr-shrm-cp]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea92c4de0a116]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 14:07:02 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 04 2023 22:06:35 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b5f868366beb71daa9de7f_Cichacki_Hayley.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Hayley Cichacki, PHR, SHRM-CP, Vice President of Human Resources.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President of Human Resources]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Hayley leads the Human Resources Department and is focused on collaborating with the leadership team to craft the company’s vision and mission in developing strategic HR plans.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Hayley leads the Human Resources Department and is focused on collaborating with the leadership team to craft the...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[12]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Isaac Hagerman]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[isaac-hagerman]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9fa98e0a102]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Fri Nov 04 2022 22:27:43 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Mon Mar 13 2023 19:08:56 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Mon Mar 13 2023 19:09:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae86a61c7b38be65a3e0_Hagerman_Isaac.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Isaac Hagerman, Chief Partnership Officer]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Partnership Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[With over 16 years’ leadership experience in the field of senior housing, Isaac has a proven track record of bringing exceptional health services to senior living communities all across the country. As Chief Partnership Officer for EmpowerMe Wellness, he oversees the implementation and management of our integrated healthcare platform at hundreds of communities nationwide. Isaac started his career with a family-owned Skilled Nursing and Assisted Living provider in Southern California. He went on to serve as Chief Operating Officer for a clinical consulting firm specializing in Assisted Living and Memory Care clinical practices, and later, as Vice President of Health and Quality for a senior housing provider with 32 communities operating in six states. Isaac has served on several nonprofit boards and committees and has been highly active as an advocate for local and state public policy.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[With over 16 years’ leadership experience in the field of senior housing, Isaac has a proven track record of bringing exceptional health services to senior living communities all across the country.]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[3]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[James L. Smith]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[james-l-smith]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9a967e0a10f]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:59:01 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 21:01:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af93c6c0f9be7f49b100_Smith_James.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[James L. Smith, Senior Vice President & General Counsel.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Senior Vice President & General Counsel]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As Senior Vice President & General Counsel at EmpowerMe, James directs the legal department. Prior to EmpowerMe, James was a founding partner at Kamykowski, Gavin & Smith, where his practice focused on defending healthcare providers in various aspects of civil litigation. During his 20+ years as a defense attorney James also defended large corporations in various legal actions and represented individuals in federal criminal matters, including claims involving anti-kickback issues. James received his undergraduate degree from Maryville University. He received his law degree from Washington University School of Law in St. Louis.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As Senior Vice President & General Counsel at EmpowerMe, James directs the legal department. Prior to EmpowerMe, James was a founding partner at Kamykowski, Gavin & Smith...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[9]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Jami Gruenloh]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[jami-gruenloh]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea96e13e0a101]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Aug 30 2022 19:59:56 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:38:54 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae7cc6c0f985dd49968d_Gruenloh_Jami.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Jami Gruenloh]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[therapy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Jami is a Physical Therapist with 25+ years of clinical experience. She graduated from St Louis University with a bachelor’s degree in physical therapy. Jami has treated in a variety of settings including acute rehab, outpatient, skilled nursing, and assisted living communities. Jami is a certified lymphedema therapist and is also an Otago certified falls prevention specialist. She has served in a management role for the last 15 years and thoroughly enjoys coaching and mentoring other therapists. Jami is a Medicare surveyor with AAAASF. Jami lives in O’Fallon IL with her husband and 2 boys. She enjoys playing tennis and spending time with her family]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Jami is a Physical Therapist with 25+ years of clinical experience. She graduated from St Louis University with a bachelor’s degree in physical therapy. Jami has treated in a variety of settings including acute rehab, outpatient, skilled nursing, and assisted living communities. ]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[34]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Janet Tiemeyer]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[janet-tiemeyer]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9accce09fc6]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 14:10:35 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 22:07:48 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/626d8301d608a4b4e69a2743_61e03245338ad6fb6c8ddda1_Janet_Tiemeyer.jpeg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Janet Tiemeyer, Regional Vice President of Sales]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Sales]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[With over 24 years of nursing experience and 13 of those being in senior living, Janet has spent her time working to improve the quality of care for those served. While working in senior living, she has focused her time on identifying opportunities and collaborating with team members to improve systems and processes that result in better outcomes for residents, team members, and organizations. Previously as the Senior Vice President of Quality and Risk Management with Elegance Living, Janet led the organization’s COVID-19 response which included proactive109 steps to mitigate risk and keep residents and team members safe. She’s a participant in the International Council on Active Aging (ICAA) and has presented for state associations, organizational boards as well as government officials. As Vice President of Clinical Integration, Janet will be focused on building and integrating clinical programs and processes to support the growth of EmpowerMe Wellness]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[With over 24 years of nursing experience and 13 of those being in senior living, Janet has spent her time working to improve the quality of care for those served...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[13]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Jennifer Keeney, MOT, OTR/L, CDS]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[jennifer-keeney-mot-otr-l-cds]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9c413e0a115]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:01:45 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 04 2023 22:06:15 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b5f838379433842049094a_Keeney_Jenn.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Jennifer Keeney, MOT, OTR/L, CDS, Division Vice President of Operations]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Division Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Jennifer is an AOTA certified Occupational Therapist and Operations Leader with over 15 years of experience working with the geriatric population. Jennifer holds a Master of Occupational Therapy degree from the University of Florida and has extensive training in neuromuscular intervention including a LSVT-BIG certification. Jennifer is also a PWR! Moves certified therapist, Rock Steady Boxing certified instructor, as well as a Certified Dementia Practitioner. She is currently pursuing continuing education for a certificate in Gerontology from Bellarmine University. Jennifer resides in Floral City, Florida with her family.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Jennifer is an AOTA certified Occupational Therapist and Operations Leader with over 15 years of experience working with the geriatric population. Jennifer holds a Master...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[10]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Jesse Voyles, PT, MPT]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[jesse-voyles-pt-mpt]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9203ce0a112]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:07:15 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 21:06:44 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4afc44038957fc76f0ec3_Voyles_Jesse.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Jesse Voyles, PT, MPT, Division Vice President of Operations]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Division Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Jesse is a Physical Therapist with 12 years of clinical experience in the SNF and ALF settings. She has a Master of Physical Therapy degree from Maryville University, is certified in Vestibular Rehabilitation and OTAGO fall prevention, and is an APTA member. Jesse has spent her career providing person-centered care to the senior population and is a passionate advocate for her patients and co-workers. Her interests include being active, spending time outdoors with her family, reading, and watching sappy Hallmark movies. Jesse currently lives in O’Fallon, Missouri with her husband and three children.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Jesse is a Physical Therapist with 12 years of clinical experience in the SNF and ALF settings. She has a Master of Physical Therapy degree from Maryville University...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[11]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[John M. Howell, Jr.]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[john-m-howell-jr]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea937d0e0a103]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:55:23 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:56:31 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae9b79123373bbec713b_Howell_John.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[John M. Howell, Jr., ]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Marketing & Experience Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Chief Marketing and Experience Officer at EmpowerMe Wellness, John leads the brand marketing, digital, corporate communications, and customer success teams. As a long-time sales and CPG-trained marketing professional, Howell brings over 25 years of experience to his focus on B2B and B2C acquisition and retention initiatives. He has a passion for leading cross-functional teams that make strategic changes to benefit both the consumer and the business. Prior to his current role, Howell was the Vice President of CX & Marketing at Centene Corporation, a Fortune 50 healthcare provider. While at Centene for six years, he managed the company’s consumer experience initiatives, brand marketing, digital transformation, strategic insights, loyalty & rewards, and the corporate creative teams.
While at Enterprise Holdings Inc. for over 11 years, Howell led the research, creative development, execution, and all strategic brand marketing initiatives for the company’s rental, truck, fleet acquisition, and remarketing businesses. In addition to these segments, he worked to build vital partnerships with manufacturers through innovative co-marketing programs. He was also responsible for overseeing brand advertising and all marketing activities for the company’s franchise operations in Mexico and South America.
Howell began his career in sales and trade marketing with Procter & Gamble in 1987. From there, he joined the pet food marketing team at Nestle/Purina Company where he was the brand manager on Puppy Chow. In 1997, he became the brand director for Roundup weed killer in Monsanto’s agriculture division. Howell joined Maryville Consulting, a private IT consulting firm, in 2000 as its vice president of sales and marketing.
Howell is a native of St. Louis. He received his Bachelor of Arts in economics from Vanderbilt University and his Master of Business Administration from the John M. Olin School of Business at Washington University.
Howell and his wife, Virginia, reside in St. Louis with their three children and two dogs.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Chief Marketing and Experience Officer at EmpowerMe Wellness, John leads the brand marketing, digital, corporate communications, and customer success teams...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[6]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Joseph “Jody” Mitchell, MD ]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[joseph-jody-mitchell-md]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9c1b4e0a10a]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Apr 27 2022 21:17:18 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:56:04 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af2f26e16f7296a568fd_Mitchell_Jody.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Joseph “Jody” Mitchell, MD, Chief Medical Officer.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Medical Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Chief Medical Officer of EmpowerMe Wellness, Dr. Joseph “Jody” Mitchell oversees and manages clinical practices, focuses on staff development for field clinicians, and utilizes the most current research and practices to provide better outcomes for residents of senior living communities nationwide. As an experienced healthcare leader, Dr. Mitchell brings over a decade of experience to his role. He has an eye on the future of healthcare, with a persistent drive to use technology to create better medical outcomes. But most importantly, he has a deep, life-long passion for improving the lives of seniors. Prior to coming to EmpowerMe Wellness, Dr. Mitchell served the clinicians, patients, and families of Owensboro Health in Owensboro, Kentucky, most recently in the roles of Medical Director of Outpatient Services and Medical Director of Athletic Training Services. He also served as Owensboro Health’s Medical Director of Healthpark, Kentucky’s only facility certified by the national Medical Fitness Association. Originally a Kentucky native, Dr. Mitchell recently relocated to St. Louis with his wife, Kate, and their three children. In addition to earning a Doctor of Medicine degree with a clinical focus on primary care in 2011 from the University of Kentucky, Dr. Mitchell is currently pursuing a Master of Business Administration degree from Western Kentucky University. He completed his Family Medicine residency and a Sports Medicine fellowship from the University of Kentucky in 2015 and 2016, respectively, and received the Resident Teacher of the Year Award in 2014 and 2015. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Chief Medical Officer of EmpowerMe Wellness, Dr. Joseph “Jody” Mitchell oversees and manages clinical practices, focuses on staff development for field clinicians...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[4]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Joshua Stevens]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[joshua-stevens]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea92933e0a111]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:57:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:44:02 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4afafbad4718988d748f3_Stevens_Josh.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Joshua Stevens, Founder and Chief Executive Officer.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Founder and Chief Executive Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Josh is an entrepreneur and leader with a passion for improving the lives of elders. He has vast experience in the senior housing and senior care industry. As a mission-driven entrepreneur and founder, Josh had developed, owned, operated, and acquired more than 40 senior housing communities across the Midwest and Southeast prior to founding EmpowerMe Wellness. His experience as a senior housing operator is what led him to found EmpowerMe, with the belief that there is a huge opportunity for positive change in the healthcare services sector of the industry. Josh’s dedication to serving seniors began more than 18 years ago when he spent several years working on the front lines of hospice agencies. He holds a Bachelor of Science in Business from Eastern Illinois University and a Juris Doctorate, cum laude, from Washington University in St. Louis. Prior to undergraduate studies, Josh was an enlisted member of the United States Marine Corps. He resides in St. Louis, Missouri, with his wife of 15 years and three children. He is a long-standing member of The Journey Church in St. Louis, serves as a member of the Board of Trustees of Niagara University, a member of the Board of Directors of NIC MAP Vision, a member of the Executive Board of the American Seniors Housing Organization, a member of Young Presidents Organization and a member of the Chairs Council of Greater St. Louis.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Josh is an entrepreneur and leader with a passion for improving the lives of elders. He has vast experience in the senior housing and senior care industry. As a mission-driven entrepreneur and founder...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[1]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Julia Baechle, MOTR/L, CDP]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[julia-baechle-motr-l]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea98488e0a0f8]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Jul 12 2022 14:30:29 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:34:41 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ad7f8b2a2709c78c77d0_Baechle_Julia.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President of Clinical Services and Wellness Programming]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the VP of Clinical Services for EmpowerMe Wellness, Julia Baechle oversees clinical quality, programming, education, training, and support for field clinicians. With a passion for life-long learning, she focuses on utilizing the latest literature and evidence to achieve clinical excellence, resulting in better outcomes for seniors. She also spends time identifying opportunities for collaboration and integration of clinical services to promote a comprehensive, holistic approach to health and wellness. Julia is an Occupational Therapist with over 10 years of experience working with older adults in Outpatient, Assisted Living, Independent Living, and Memory Care settings as a treating therapist, Rehab Manager, and Rehab Agency Administrator. She obtained her master’s degree in Occupational Therapy from Maryville University in St. Louis, MO. Julia is an active member of NARA, AOTA, International Council on Active Aging, and has presented for state and national associations. Julia lives in St. Charles, MO with her husband, son, daughter, and their Golden Retriever, Leo. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the VP of Clinical Services for EmpowerMe Wellness, Julia Baechle oversees clinical quality, programming, education, training, and support for field clinicians...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[18]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kathi Price, RN]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kathi-price-rn]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea95678e0a10d]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:37:45 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:42:52 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af6a13a7d91ffaf01b54_Price_Kathi.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kathi Price, RN, RN Consultant, Pharmacy.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacy]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[pharmacy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[RN Consultant, Pharmacy]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Kathi has been with EverSpring Pharmacy since 2014. She has over 35 years of long-term care experience, with 20 years as an RN Consultant for a national LTC pharmacy, and has also held the position of Director of Nursing. Kathi offers exceptional customer service and has a deep understanding of the ever-changing senior care environment.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Kathi has been with EverSpring Pharmacy since 2014. She has over 35 years of long-term care experience, with 20 years as an RN Consultant for a national LTC pharmacy, and has also held the position of Director of Nursing...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[23]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kelly Modaff]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kelly-madoff-2]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea96d0ce0a10b]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Aug 30 2022 20:15:30 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 04 2023 18:06:13 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af3efcbe52e1163362ff_Modaff_Kelly.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kelly Madoff]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[therapy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Kelly is a Doctor of Physical Therapy with nearly five years of experience working with the geriatric population in a variety of settings, including Outpatient, Independent Living, Assisted Living, and Memory Care. Kelly received her doctoral degree in Physical Therapy from the University of Kentucky. Since graduating, Kelly has been an active member of the APTA and KPTA and achieved her board certification as a geriatric specialist in June of 2022. As a Regional Vice President of Operations, she uses her skills to promote patient-centered and evidence-based care for the elderly. Kelly lives in Louisville, KY with her husband and enjoys running, hiking, and biking throughout the area. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Kelly is a Doctor of Physical Therapy with nearly five years of experience working with the geriatric population in a variety of settings, including Outpatient, Independent Living, Assisted Living, and Memory Care.]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[35]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kenneth H. Hannah]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kenneth-h-hannah]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea97db4e0a118]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:30:14 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Feb 15 2023 17:13:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Wed Feb 15 2023 17:13:45 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63bf1c097e9f27f11c4530ad_Ken%20Hannah-web.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kenneth H. Hannah, Chief Operating Officer]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Operating Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Ken is a highly motivated and effective leader with recognized expertise in finance and operations. For over 30 years, he has been personally responsible for growing companies big and small, and developing numerous Fortune 1000 leaders during his career. As Chief Operating Officer for EmpowerMe Wellness, he manages operations and finances across our nationwide footprint, ensuring we continue to grow to meet the ever-expanding needs of our aging population. Most recently, Ken served as Chief Financial Officer for Caleres, Inc., a 144-year-old, $3 billion global footwear company. Prior to joining Caleres, Hannah served as Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer to JCPenney, was named Executive Vice President and President of Solar Energy at MEMC Electronic Materials, Inc., and held senior executive leadership positions in finance and operations with The Home Depot, The Boeing Company and General Electric. Ken holds an MBA in International Business from Saint Louis University and a Bachelor of Science degree in Finance from Southern Illinois University Carbondale. He and his wife Amy have five children. He is a member of the Board of Directors for the St. Louis Zoo Association and Meta Materials, Inc., and he serves on the External Advisory Board at Southern Illinois University Carbondale.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Ken is a highly motivated and effective leader with recognized expertise in finance and operations. ]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[2]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kevin Brockmeyer ]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kevin-brockmeyer]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea96c2ce0a0fb]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Fri Feb 25 2022 04:58:19 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:36:14 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4addbbad471a05cd71c92_Brockmeyer_Kevin.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kevin Brockmeyer, Chief Financial Officer, Pharmacy.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacy]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[pharmacy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Financial Officer, Pharmacy ]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Kevin started his own long-term care pharmacy in 2012, servicing patients in Missouri and Illinois. After exiting that pharmacy as part of a merger with PharMerica in 2016, he served as a consultant for long-term care pharmacies across the country. In August 2018, Kevin became Chief Financial Officer of EverSpring Pharmacy to oversee that company's strategic growth and development. His efforts supported EverSpring's partnership with EmpowerMe Wellness, which began in 2021.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Kevin started his own long-term care pharmacy in 2012, servicing patients in Missouri and Illinois. After exiting that pharmacy as part of a merger with PharMerica in 2016, he served as a consultant for long-term care pharmacies across the country...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[4]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kirsten Bergman, COC]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kirsten-bergman-coc]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea903c9e0a0f9]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Mon Jan 17 2022 11:44:55 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:35:22 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ada926e16fafc9a54a3b_Bergman_Kirsten.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kirsten Bergman, COC, Vice President of Revenue Cycle Management.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President of Revenue Cycle Management]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Kirsten is a Certified Outpatient Coder with over 17 years of experience directing all aspects of the revenue cycle of outpatient therapy. She holds AAPC and Lean Six Sigma Green Belt certifications and a Bachelor of Business Administration with a focus in Management from Truman State University. She enjoys the face-paced environment EmpowerMe offers and knowing each part of the company delivers an impeccable service to our senior community. Kirsten lives in St. Louis, MO with her husband and their two children. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Kirsten is a Certified Outpatient Coder with over 17 years of experience directing all aspects of the revenue cycle of outpatient therapy...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[17]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Kristy Kennedy]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[kristy-kennedy]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9dbe1e0a105]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 14:00:32 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:40:03 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4aec08991fa2fa6d2bbae_Kennedy_Kristy.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Kristy Kennedy, Vice President of Partnership Success.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Vice President of Partnership Success]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Kristy joined EmpowerMe as the Vice President of Partnership Success. Her focus is on partnering with clients to develop occupancy growth initiatives and support their business development goals. She brings over 15 years of sales leadership experience in senior living. Kristy spent 10 years as a Regional Director of Sales & Marketing with Sunrise Senior Living, one of the country’s top 5 largest senior living providers. While working at Sunrise, Kristy created and led the first regional Business Development team, focused solely on increasing referrals and move-ins, by creating a robust referral source pipeline across hospital and healthcare systems in target market areas. She is a Certified Professional Co-Active Coach through The Coaches Training Institute and holds a bachelor’s degree from Appalachian State University. She lives in Washington DC with her wife of 28 years and has three adult children.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Kristy joined EmpowerMe as the Vice President of Partnership Success. Her focus is on partnering with clients to develop occupancy growth initiatives and support their business development goals...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[11]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Laine Thies, CNP, ANP]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[laine-thies-cnp-anp]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea96998e09110]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 16:58:49 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:41:52 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Waiting on Bio and photo ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Lauren Petry, NP]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[lauren-petry-np]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea96581e09ec1]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 15:40:03 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:41:25 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/62a0bdac629296e4e9e7e440_Petry_L-min.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Lauren Petry]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As an Adult-Geriatric Nurse Practitioner, Lauren will bring over 15 years of health care experience to building relationships with and providing quality care for the senior living communities she serves. She is motivated to partner with each resident in the pursuit of enriching their lives– physically, mentally, and emotionally. Lauren feels honored to be invited to practice medicine in the residents’ homes. She will focus on coordinating with other team members to provide individualized care, detect illnesses early on and prevent the need for higher levels of treatment. Lauren graduated from Saint Louis University with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing. For almost a decade, she worked at various hospitals in the St. Louis area with a focus in intensive care and neurosciences. In 2016, she graduated from Maryville University with her Master of Science in Nursing. As an Adult- Geriatric Nurse Practitioner, her focus has been on Neurology and Geriatric Medicine. Lauren lives in Springfield, Missouri, and enjoys reading, the great outdoors, HGTV, history, and spoiling her dog, Fergus. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As an Adult-Geriatric Nurse Practitioner, Lauren will bring over 15 years of health care experience to building relationships with and providing quality care for the senior living communities she serves...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[2]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Lisa Meyer PT, MBA]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[lisa-meyer-pt-mba]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea97657e0a109]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 14:48:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 21:05:42 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4af10c6c0f95d4249a248_Meyer_Lisa.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Lisa Meyer PT, MBA, Senior Vice President of University Relations.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Senior Vice President of University Relations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[With over 30 years in the rehab industry, Lisa was recruited specifically to lead the launch of EmpowerMe in 2017. Formerly, Lisa spent 20+ years at RehabCare, one of the largest providers of post-acute rehab services in the country. There, as Division VP, she had full P&L responsibility of over 350 clinics located in senior living communities across the Midwest with annual revenue exceeding $120 million. Lisa holds a Bachelor of Science in Physical Therapy from St. Louis University and a Master of Business Administration from Maryville University. She has been a licensed PT for 34 years. Lisa lives in Columbia, Illinois on her family ranch and has two adult children.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[With over 30 years in the rehab industry, Lisa was recruited specifically to lead the launch of EmpowerMe in 2017. Formerly, Lisa spent 20+ years at RehabCare...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[10]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Lucas Donnelley]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[lucas-donnelley]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea959f0e0a100]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:49:59 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 20:56:48 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae6d8991faa98ed2b57b_Donnolley_Lucas_2.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Lucas Donnelley, Managing Director.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Managing Director]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Lucas joined the team in 2020 as Managing Director of EmpowerMe Holdings. Prior to EmpowerMe, Lucas was the Managing Director of Dreampact Ventures, an early-stage Venture Capital firm. Lucas created and ran the Dreampact due diligence and deal flow processes, as well as managing the day-to-day operations of the firm. Lucas started his career with J.P. Morgan, where he worked in New York with executive leadership in the Wealth Management business to develop and execute the firm’s highest strategic priorities. Lucas graduated with honors from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Lucas joined the team in 2020 as Managing Director of EmpowerMe Holdings. Prior to EmpowerMe, Lucas was the Managing Director of Dreampact Ventures...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[7]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Lucija Sadl, MSN, AGPCNP-BC, NP-C]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[lucija-sadl]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9ffcce09ebc]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 15:09:54 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:40:29 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/62a0bb8e05476e082312b8a8_Sadi_L-min.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Lucija Sadl]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Lucija Sadl has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care. As a seasoned nurse practitioner, Lucija brings over 25 years of combined experience in Acute Rehab, Family Medicine, Cardiac, Cardiothoracic, Medical ICU & Telemetry Care. Lucija has a passion for delivering exceptional patient care and is solutions-focused, collaborating with healthcare peers to optimize patient outcomes per treatment goals. Lucija joins EmpowerMe with an extensive portfolio as an advanced Nurse Practitioner, working for the top hospital systems in the St. Louis metro area, including Barnes Jewish Hospital, SSM-St. Mary’s, and SSM DePaul. She most recently spent the past 7 years at St. Luke’s Des Peres Hospital. Lucija received her Bachelor of Science in Nursing with honors from Saint Louis University and her Master of Arts in Nursing from Goldfarb School of Nursing at Barnes-Jewish College. She holds dual board certifications for the National Nurse Practitioner Board and is currently licensed as a Registered Nurse in the states of Missouri and Illinois.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Lucija Sadl has the primary responsibility for the planning, implementation, and management of all resident health care needs, including urgent conditions, routine examinations, and collaboration of care...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[3]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Matthew Porter]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[matthew-porter]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea99e82e09ec2]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 13:46:34 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 22:09:44 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/61e02d1347a48f2ec00db8e1_Matthew%20Porter.jpeg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Matthew Porter, Chief Technology Officer]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Chief Technology Officer]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As Chief Technology Officer of EmpowerMe, Matthew is focused on building EmpowerMe’s tech-enabled strategy across the organization. Prior to EmpowerMe, Matthew was CEO of Invisibly, a disruptive technology company backed by Founder’s Fund. Prior to Invisibly, Matthew founded Contegix, an award-winning, managed hosting, cloud computing, and colocation service provider in St. Louis, Missouri. In 2016, Matthew merged two companies into Contegix and sold a majority stake to Strattam Capital. He still serves as Vice Chairman. Matthew is a father to three amazing kids, husband to a phenomenal woman, geek, trail runner, and ultramarathoner.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As Chief Technology Officer of EmpowerMe, Matthew is focused on building EmpowerMe’s tech-enabled strategy across the organization...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[3]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Mick Blazier, R.Ph. PharmD]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[mick-blazier-r-ph-pharmd]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea97607e0a0fa]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:32:31 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:35:51 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4adc1f6d3902f9425568c_Blazier_Mick.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Mick Blazier, R.Ph. PharmD, Director of Operations, Pharmacy.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacy]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Director of Operations, Pharmacy]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Mick has over 14 years of Long-Term Care experience. He has been with EverSpring since its inception in 2008. Having been involved in the startup and growth of EverSpring, Mick offers an understanding of every role in an LTC Pharmacy, and his tenure will bring success in his role of pharmaceutical operations under the integration of healthcare services at EmpowerMe Wellness.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Mick has over 14 years of Long-Term Care experience. He has been with EverSpring since its inception in 2008. Having been involved in the startup and growth of EverSpring....]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[21]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Nick Hughes]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[nick-hughes]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9c8a5e0a104]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 16:24:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:39:37 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4aea7a61c7b284165a5d0_Hughes_Nick.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Nick Hughes President Southeast]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Coporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[President, Southeast]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the President of EmpowerMe Wellness, Southeast, Nick Hughes manages the sales process and business development throughout the Southeast US. A leader in the therapy/rehab and healthcare industry, Nick brings over 14 years of experience to his role at EmpowerMe. He has a passion for allowing seniors to age in place and thrive in their new environment. Prior to his current role, Nick was CEO of Salus Physical Therapy, one of the largest providers of physical and occupational therapy to the senior living space throughout Florida. Nick received his Doctorate of Physical Therapy degree from University at Buffalo after his undergraduate work at Fordham University in New York City. Nick is a native of Buffalo, NY and currently lives in the Tampa Bay Area with his wife Bethany and two daughters, Olivia, and Emerson. When he is not working and collaborating with our incredible senior living partners, Nick is outside and being active with his friends and family. ]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the President of EmpowerMe Wellness, Southeast, Nick Hughes manages the sales process and business development throughout the Southeast...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[14]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Nicole Lord, MSN, FNP-BC]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[nicole-lord]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea95ea0e09fca]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 16:57:35 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:42:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/6320ad91b003291b557ae006_Lord_N_2.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Nicole Lord serves to provide education, general and preventative care, conduct check-ups, treat illnesses, order lab tests, and prescribe medications as needed within the senior living community. Nicole is a board-certified Family Nurse Practitioner who partners with Dr. Michael Koeppen. She brings over 15 years of experience as a medical professional and has a passion for functioning in interdisciplinary medical teams to provide maximal benefit to her patients. Prior to her current role, Nicole served in roles as a Clinical Network Manager at Signify Health, a Family Practice Primary Care Provider at Decatur Memorial Hospital, a Women’s Health Nurse Practitioner in a private practice, an independent provider at Whole Body Medical Wellness, and an Adjunct Clinical Instructor at the University of Illinois and Millikin University nursing programs. Nicole is a native of Illinois and has also lived in Louisiana and Michigan. She began her career when she enlisted in the United States Army at the age of 17. She earned the rank of Sergeant, served as a prestigious member of the Illinois Honor Guard, and worked as a certified Drill Instructor with at-risk youth at Lincoln’s Challenge Academy. She received an Associate in General Science and an Associate in Applied Science from Parkland College, a Bachelor of Science in Nursing from Illinois State University, and a Master of Science in Nursing from Olivet Nazarene University. Nicole and her husband, James, reside in Clinton, Illinois with their two daughters and two dogs. She enjoys spending time with family, volunteering as a Faith Community Nurse (FCN), and traveling.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Nicole Lord serves to provide education, general and preventative care, conduct check-ups, treat illnesses, order lab tests, and prescribe medications as needed within the senior living community.]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[37]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Nicole Lord, MSN, FNP-BC]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[nicole-lord-msn-fnp-bc]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea933cfe09fcb]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Mon Sep 19 2022 19:12:57 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 22:01:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/6320ad91b003291b557ae006_Lord_N_2.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Nicole Lord]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Nicole Lord serves to provide education, general and preventative care, conduct check-ups, treat illnesses, order lab tests, and prescribe medications as needed within the senior living community. Nicole is a board-certified Family Nurse Practitioner with Full Practice Authority. She brings over 15 years of experience as a medical professional and has a passion for functioning in interdisciplinary medical teams to provide maximal benefit to her patients. Prior to her current role, Nicole served in roles as a Clinical Network Manager at Signify Health, a Family Practice Primary Care Provider at Decatur Memorial Hospital, a Women’s Health Nurse Practitioner in a private practice, an independent provider at Whole Body Medical Wellness, and an Adjunct Clinical Instructor at the University of Illinois and Millikin University nursing programs. Nicole is a native of Illinois and has also lived in Louisiana and Michigan. She began her career when she enlisted in the United States Army at the age of 17. She earned the rank of Sergeant, served as a prestigious member of the Illinois Honor Guard, and worked as a certified Drill Instructor with at-risk youth at Lincoln’s Challenge Academy. She received an Associate in General Science and an Associate in Applied Science from Parkland College, a Bachelor of Science in Nursing from Illinois State University, and a Master of Science in Nursing from Olivet Nazarene University. Nicole and her husband, James, reside in Clinton, Illinois with their two daughters and two dogs. She enjoys spending time with family, volunteering as a Faith Community Nurse (FCN), and traveling.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness, Nicole Lord serves to provide education, general and preventative care, conduct check-ups, treat illnesses, order lab tests, and prescribe medications as needed within the senior living community...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[37]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Pamela Albacete]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[pam-albacete]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea94437e0a0f6]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Aug 16 2022 21:09:14 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:34:00 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ad53ef6aaf74c0ea09af_Albacete_Pamela.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Pamela Albacete]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy Leadership ]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[therapy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Regional Vice President of Operations]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Pam received her master’s degree in Speech-Language Pathology and then further training/certifications as a Dementia Care Specialist, Dementia Care trainer, Vital-Stim certified, SPEAKOut! certified, NMES the Guardian Way, and MBS-Imp training. She has been improving the lives of seniors as an Operations Leader for over 20 years with major therapy companies that serve IL, AL, MC, SNF, hospital, Adult Day programs, in-home therapy, and a specialty physician group. Pam and her spouse of 25-plus years enjoy traveling, exploring, and cooking together while living in the beautiful mountains of North Carolina.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Pam received her master’s degree in Speech-Language Pathology and then further training/certifications as a Dementia Care Specialist, Dementia Care trainer, Vital-Stim certified, SPEAKOut! certified, NMES the Guardian Way, and MBS-Imp training...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[31]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Person A]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[person-a]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea9e8c2e09123]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed May 25 2022 16:46:21 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 01 2022 14:06:08 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[3]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Shea Long]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[shea-long]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9da57e0a107]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 27 2022 18:14:38 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Wed Jan 11 2023 21:04:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4aee213a7d92719f00ec1_Long_Shea.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Senior Vice President of Product]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Leadership]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[corporate-leadership]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Senior Vice President of Product]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As the SVP of Product at EmpowerMe Wellness, Shea leads the Product, Payer Strategy and Technology teams. As a long-time Product and Technology professional, Shea brings over 25 years of experience to his focus on B2B and B2C Product initiatives that drive growth and enhanced customer experiences. He has a passion for leading cross-functional teams that make strategic solutions to benefit both the resident/patient and the business. Shea has brought Human Centered Design techniques to the business to deliver exceptional Product experiences. Prior to his current role, Shea led the Product organization at ModivCare (the largest Social Determinants of Health solutions provider in the nation). He was responsible for building a Product organization from the ground up to deliver Mobile Application solutions for Members to engage with their care, Home Delivery Solutions for Medical Necessitated Meals, Remote Patient Monitoring solutions, and Medication Adherence capabilities. While at Centene, Shea was the Staff Vice President of Commercial Innovation at Centene Corporation, a Fortune 50 healthcare provider. He led the development of new capabilities to drive dramatically improved digital member experiences via mobile app solutions, significant member engagement in their healthcare, rural healthcare initiatives and Social Determinants of Health solutions. Shea was seen as a pioneer in the payer space in his use of Lyft as a tool to close Access to Care issues related to transportation. In addition to these accomplishments, he is known as a leader in developing vital partnerships with providers through innovative technology integrations and business models. Shea began his career in Product Development with Space Systems Division in the U.S. Air Force AT&T in 1988 building classified satellite systems. From there, he joined the AT&T Product team at AT&T Wireless developing mobile solutions for business and consumer clients. From there, he went on to work at high growth companies such as Savvis and TierPoint in the Cloud Services space. Shea is a native of St. Louis. He received his Bachelor of Science in Business from the U.S. Air Force Academy and has a certificate from Stanford University’s Graduate School of Business for Corporate Innovation. Shea and his wife, Heidi, reside in St. Louis with their two daughters.]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As the SVP of Product at EmpowerMe Wellness, Shea leads the Product, Payer Strategy and Technology teams. As a long-time Product and Technology professional, Shea brings over 25 years of experience to his focus on B2B and B2C Product initiatives that drive growth and enhanced customer experiences...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[9]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Steve McConnell]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[steve-mcconnell]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9bf77e0a108]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:31:39 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:40:47 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4aeedd4ef7255f5ecfd57_McConnell_Steve.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Steve McConnell, President, Pharmacy]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacy]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[pharmacy]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[President, Pharmacy]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Steve founded EverSpring Pharmacy in 2008 and has specialized in medication compliance pharmacy since 1993. As President of EverSpring under the new partnership with EmpowerMe Wellness, Steve leads the pharmaceutical service line that serves senior living communities. Steve brings a wealth of industry expertise, having held several positions in the Midwest within the long-term care pharmaceutical industry including consulting pharmacist, operational clinician, executive director, and regional director of a long-term care pharmacy. Steve has earned specialized certificates in geriatric medicine from colleges such as the University of the Sciences in Philadelphia and Harvard University. Steve graduated with his Bachelor's Degree in 1993 from the St. Louis College of Pharmacy and with his Master's of Business Administration in 2002 from St. Louis University. Steve has served on several long-term care advisory boards and was a previous Arch Grants Advisory Council Member.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Steve founded EverSpring Pharmacy in 2008 and has specialized in medication compliance pharmacy since 1993...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[1]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Theresa Catalano]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[theresa-catalano]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea916b8e0a0fd]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:25:11 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:37:13 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4ae0e26e16ff530a55650_Catalano_Theresa.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Theresa Catalano, Laboratory Director.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Diagnostics]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Laboratory Director]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As Laboratory Director at EmpowerMe Wellness, Theresa manages the day-to-day operations of the laboratory. This includes managing coworkers, overseeing the quality and maintenance of the instruments as well as productivity standards. She has over 15 years of laboratory experience from working the bench as a medical technologist to managing a full-service hospital laboratory including time at MU Healthcare and the Mercy system in St. Louis. Theresa enjoys improving the lab workflows to be as efficient as possible in the ever-changing lab world. A native of the St. Louis area, Theresa received her Bachelor of Science in Clinical Laboratory Science from Marquette University and her Master of Public Health from the University of Missouri.
Theresa and her husband, Michael, reside in Wildwood, MO.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As Laboratory Director at EmpowerMe Wellness, Theresa manages the day-to-day operations of the laboratory...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[17]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Toni Depriest, MSN, FNP-C]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[toni-depriest-msn-fnp-c]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea983a9e09fc8]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Jun 08 2022 16:56:55 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Fri Oct 28 2022 15:42:27 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/630e6c868dbf5fef1263b838_Depriest_T1.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Toni Depriest]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Nurse Practitioner]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[nurse-practitioner]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Toni is a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness. She has a fearless passion for her career and helping others. Her focus is more than just writing orders, she is committed to seeing patients get the best healthcare treatment they need. She has expertise in wound care and fall reduction. She is an advocate for physical therapy, encouraging and referring residents for evaluations and believes therapy, especially physical therapy, is important to stay strong to maintain and gain independence. She believes prevention is the best medicine. Toni is the youngest of six kids and attended St. Charles Community College for her RN and associate degree. She received her bachelor's and master's for her Nurse Practitioner Certification from the University of Missouri- St. Louis. She lives in St. Charles, MO in a house she built 22 years ago with her three fur babies. One long-haired Chihuahua boy named Chewy, and two German Shepard girls named Sophia and Emmie. Toni has one adult son named Brandon and a young granddaughter named Alba. She loves to bike ride, go for walks with her dogs, and read. Her favorite activity is to watch a good movie.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Toni is a Nurse Practitioner at EmpowerMe Wellness. She has a fearless passion for her career and helping others. Her focus is more than just writing orders, she is committed to seeing patients get the best healthcare treatment they need.]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[36]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Tyler Witges, MLS (ASCP), MHA]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[tyler-witges-mls-ascp-mha]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9e7cfe0a113]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:18:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:44:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4afdb13a7d9280cf020d3_Witges_Tyler.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Tyler Witges, MLS (ASCP), MHA, President, Diagnostics.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Diagnostics]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[diagnostics]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[President, Diagnostics]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[As President of Diagnostics at EmpowerMe Wellness, Tyler is charged with the overall operation of the Diagnostics division. This includes contracting, instrument procurement, vendor relations, and finance. Tyler has over 15 years of experience in the laboratory field with duties ranging from phlebotomist to Executive Director of Laboratory Services at Mercy St. Louis where he oversaw a laboratory operation of more than 250 coworkers for three years. He has spent his years in laboratory leadership improving workflows and increasing testing capacity, both to improve patient experience and financial performance in the laboratory.
A native of Teutopolis, IL, Tyler received his Bachelor of Science in Medical Laboratory Sciences from Illinois State University and his Master of Healthcare Administration from the University of Phoenix.
Tyler and his wife Kaitlin reside in O'Fallon, MO with their three children.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[As President of Diagnostics at EmpowerMe Wellness, Tyler is charged with the overall operation of the Diagnostics division. This includes contracting, instrument...
]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[7]]></sortorder>
	</node>
	<node>
		<name><![CDATA[Yulonda Brown, PBT (ASCP)]]></name>
		<slug><![CDATA[yulonda-brown-pbt-ascp]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[63c996427b6ea97f86e08f81]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[63c996437b6ea9ab9de0a0fc]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 13 2022 15:21:23 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 03 2023 22:36:34 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Thu Jan 19 2023 19:16:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<memberimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/61d2e3c9499f212051abd992/63b4adf0ef6aaf6235ea1438_Brown_Yulonda.jpg]]></memberimage>
		<memberimagealttext><![CDATA[Yulonda Brown, PBT (ASCP), Director of Support Services.]]></memberimagealttext>
		<category><![CDATA[Diagnostics]]></category>
		<category2><![CDATA[]]></category2>
		<memberdesignation><![CDATA[Director of Support Services]]></memberdesignation>
		<membersdescription><![CDATA[Diagnostics services help residents live healthy lives without delay of treatment. Research has shown that residents who receive care in environments in which they live thrive with coming full circle with treatment. Being able to live within a community that offers services without leaving, is literally service at your front door. Initially, Yulonda’s education path took to her to nursing. While in school, she was introduced to the lab and discovered the lab is a vital part of patient healthcare. She learned that no results meant no treatment. Without results, you're only guessing. From there, Yulonda was hooked and never regretted crossing the hallway and joining the laboratory. As Director of Support Services at EmpowerMe Wellness, Yulonda has oversight of the education program and implementation of phlebotomy services at selected living communities. She has oversight of a team of phlebotomy trainers that travel throughout the regions training employees on topics related to all things phlebotomy. Yulonda has a total of 26 years of experience, with eight years dedicated to leadership, in the world of lab services related to phlebotomy, on-site and off-site lab operations. She's worked with organizations such as Mercy St. Louis, Quest Diagnostics, LabCorp, and Missouri Baptist. In her leadership roles, she’s maintained oversight of 70+ employees through cross-region management. Her specialties are education, training, process improvement/implementation, and grooming new talent.
Born and raised in St. Louis, MO, Yulonda is a certified phlebotomy technician through the ASCP and is on track to receive her bachelor’s degree in Business Management from the University of Phoenix in April of 2022. Yulonda and her husband, Chad, reside in an empty nest with their rescue dog, Vincent, in Creve Coeur, MO.
]]></membersdescription>
		<membersdescriptionexcerpt><![CDATA[Diagnostics services help residents live healthy lives without delay of treatment. Research has shown that residents who receive...]]></membersdescriptionexcerpt>
		<sortorder><![CDATA[18]]></sortorder>
	</node>
</data>
